Alright, you're done. Lets take a look at the solution.
Now we're going to need some text views. First of all lets
look at our linear layout. It's vertical. We're going to want it
to be horizontal. The next thing we're going to want are a
bunch of text views. Lets just drag them in. Now
remember we had all those ID's that were given to us
in the last quiz. The first one is the list item
date text view. And we'll give it some text that makes
sense when we help to layout the layout. We'll remove
this before we actually submit it to our project. And
for fun let's switch to landscape. It'll make things a
little more legible. Also let's just zoom in a little bit.
All right. So that's our list item date text view. Now
right next to that, we want another text view. Since we want the design to be
the same, this one doesn't need to have an ID. If you remember our
design had the date. Followed by a dash, followed
by the forecast, followed by a dash, followed by the high,
followed by a slash, followed by low. So this is just going to be a view that
contains a dash. And we can even hardcode this in. For now, then we're going to
create another text view next to that. Our
placeholder text will be a forecast, like clear.
The ID for this will be list item
forecast text view. Now we need another text view.
Once again this one's not going to have an ID, because we don't need it. And
we'll add another dash. Now we're actually getting
to the high and low forecasts. Let's say
a high of 23. One more plain text view, this one with a slash and, once
again, with no ID. And for our high
forecast, it better be list_item_high_text_view. Finally, we'll add one
more plain text view. This one will be for
our low, and of course, that means it's going to
be list_item_low_text_view. And there we have it. Our multiple text
view layout. Now we might want to make this prettier.
But this is a good start and it just plays
the four fields that we asked for. They are all
part of a linear layout. Before we actually would submit
this, lets remove the placeholder tabs for everything except for,
the static fields. We'll also have to remove these empty IDs, its
actually important to understand whats going on in these text views. And there
we have it, that's what your should look like, At least if you
want to make it look almost identical to the layout we started out
with. Of course you can go wild with these designs, and there's
a lot you can do with the layout editor and with different kinds
of layouts. We'll be learning more about that in the next lesson. Alright,
we finally get to start hooking this up to our UX. Let's go
back to forecast fragment.